(Amy:)She's right. But say the word, I got a lab
full of cocaine-addicted monkeys...
(Amy:)...with nothing to lose.
(Amy:)One of them could end up
in the back seat of her car.
(Amy:)Or her shower.
(Sheldon:)Ladies, ladies, please.
We're not here to talk about Penny.
(Sheldon:)We're here to talk about me.
I mean Einstein Von Brainstorm! Darn it.
(Sheldon:)All right, I guess the
cat's out of the bag.
(Sheldon:)Let me explain what's going on.
Ricardo is really Leon...
(Penny:)We know what's going on, Sheldon!
But what should I do?
(Bernadette:)Alex is your employee.
If she's doing something that's...
(Bernadette:)...making Leonard uncomfortable,
you should talk to her.
Oh, he's not uncomfortable at all.
He's loving it.
(Sheldon:)He's strutting around
like he's 5-foot-6.
(Penny:)What? He's loving it?
(Bernadette:)Sheldon, you need to talk to Alex
right away.
Talk to her. That's all you've got?
(Sheldon:)With a cool name like
Sheldon Cooper's Council of Ladies...
(Sheldon:)...I really expected more.
(Sheldon:)Give me back the t-shirts.